Sai Htun

1 Belmont Dr, Daly City, CA | 415-963-2493

saihtun1430@gmail.com | https://saihtun-webdev.now.sh

A 27 years old man, over 6 years of experiences in management industry and a hyper enthusiast in IT. Analytics minded and seeking for junior web developer or internship position, equipped with solid passion and candid attitude, a self-motivated and disciplined individual with a strong work ethic, superior communication and humor, Fluent in English, Chinese, Burmese.

EXPERIENCES

DEC 2012 - NOV 2013

Local Logistic Supervisor, Benhur Construction Materials Trading (Yangon, Myanmar)

JAN 2014 - APR 2015

Assistant manager, The Elephant Gold Leaf Production (Bangkok, Thailand)

JUN 2016 - NOV 2017

Secretary, SP Group off Company (Yangon, Myanmar)

- It was a group of companies and operating multi subsidiaries, mining, bakery and many more.

My responsibilities can be described in two categories, planning and operating. Planning meeting, trips and agenda for my boss and operating the company on behalf of CEO, data sourcing and sustainable development.

JAN 2018 – MAR 2019

Logistic Supervisor (Family Business), MgMgGyi Logistics (Yangon, Myanmar)

- Customer relationship, vehicles maintenance.

Education

2009 - 2012

Bachelor of Science In Physics (Taunggyi University, Myanmar)

AUG 2018

VCP-DCV 6.5 (VMware Certified Professional in Data Center Virtualization)

FEB 2020 - CURRENT

Self-teaching Javascript web development stacks.

Skills

- FRONTEND: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Vue, CSS utility libraries.
- Backend: Node.js, Express, NoSQL, MongoDB, Firebase
- Cloud: Netlify, Heroku, AWS, Vercel (previously known as Zeit)
- Able to adopt any library or framework quickly.